largely: adv. 在很大程度上
Lesson 29. Funny or not? Whether we find a joke funny or not largely depends on where we have been brought up.
第29课。有趣与否？我们是否发现一个笑话很有趣，这在很大程度上取决于我们的何处。
The sense of humor is mysteriously bound up with national characteristics.
幽默感与民族特征有关。
A. Frenchman, for instance, might find it hard to laugh at a Russian joke.
例如，法国人可能会发现很难为俄罗斯的笑话笑。
In the same way, a Russian might fail to see anything amusing in a joke which would make an Englishman laugh to.
以同样的方式，俄罗斯人可能看不到任何有趣的笑话，这会让英国人大笑。
comic: adj. 喜剧的，可笑的
Tears. Most funny stories are based on comic situations.
眼泪。大多数有趣的故事都是基于漫画的情况。
universal: adj. 普通的
In spite of national differences, certain funny situations have a universal appeal.
尽管存在国家差异，但某些有趣的情况仍具有普遍的吸引力。
No matter where you live, you would find it difficult not to laugh at.
无论您住在哪里，您都会发现很难不笑。
largely: adv. 在很大程度上
Say, Charlie Chaplin's early films however, a new type of humor, which stems largely from the US, has recently come into fashion.
假设，查理·卓别林（Charlie Chaplin）的早期电影是一种新型的幽默，主要源于美国，它最近陷入了时尚。
It is called, Sick Humor. Comedians base their jokes on tragic situation like violent death or serious accidents.
这被称为病幽默。喜剧演员开玩笑的基础是诸如暴力死亡或严重事故的悲惨局势。
distasteful: adj. 讨厌的
Many people find this sort of joke distasteful the following example of, Sick Humor, will enable.
许多人发现这种笑话令人反感，以下一个病态的幽默将使这样做。
You to judge for yourself. A man who had broken his right leg was taken to hospital a few weeks before Christmas.
您要自己判断。一个摔断右腿的男人被送往圣诞节前几周。
pester: v.   一再要求，纠缠
From the moment he arrived there, he kept on pestering his doctor to tell him when he would be able to go home.
从他到达那里的那一刻起，他一直在缠着医生告诉他何时可以回家。
dread: v.   惧怕, recovery: n.   康复
He dreaded having to spend Christmas in hospital. Though the doctors did his best, the patient's recovery was slow.
他害怕必须在医院度过圣诞节。尽管医生尽力而为，但患者的康复速度很慢。
plaster: n.   熟石膏
On Christmas day, the man still had his right leg in plaster.
在圣诞节那天，该男子仍然在石膏上右腿。
He spent a miserable day in bed thinking of all the fun he was missing.
他在床上度过了痛苦的一天，想着他失踪的所有乐趣。
console: v.   安慰，慰问
The following day, however, the doctor consoled him by telling him that his chances of being able to leave hospital in time for.
但是，第二天，医生告诉他他能够及时离开医院的机会来安慰他。
hobble: v.   瘸着腿走
New Year celebrations were good. The man took heart and, sure enough, on New Year's Eve he was able to hobble along to a party.
新年庆祝活动很好。这个人振作起来，果然，在除夕，他能够参加聚会。
compensate: v.   补偿
To compensate for his unpleasant experiences in hospital, the man drank a little more than was good for him.
为了弥补他在医院的不愉快经历，该男子喝了一点对他的好处。
In the process, he enjoyed himself thoroughly and kept telling everybody how much he hated hospitals.
在此过程中，他非常享受自己，并一直告诉所有人他讨厌医院。
He was still mumbling something about hospitals at the end of the party when he slipped on a piece.
当派对尽头，他仍然在喃喃地说医院的东西。
A vise and broke his left leg.
虎钳，摔断了他的左腿。